# Sapphy Doyle

Highly driven, experienced and multiskilled customer experience agent, with well established IT skills and recent experience in the medical and optical; service and sales field.

Stone

My main strengths include my ability to develop and learn from others and new situations whilst being able to apply myself to a vast array of challenges. I am a highly self-reliant individual with great levels of problem solving ability and critical thinking. Putting myself up to the challenge of a given situation whilst still happy to rely on the skill and experience of others where appropriately needed. This makes me a fantastic addition to any team, as I work well with others and can rely on them as well as able to be relied upon myself. My past experience has been working directly in many capacities with customers and patients meaning that I have cultivated a great attitude and highly effective work dynamic when working directly with clients, patients and colleagues alike.

#### Personal Details

Eligible to work in the UK: Yes

Highest Level of Education: GCSE or equivalent

Industry: Customer Service, Healthcare, Medical Information, Other, Retail, Sales

Total years of experience: 12

# Work Experience

### **Optical Consultant**

Specsavers - Stone July 2021 to December 2022

- Testing, processing and caring for patients in preparation for eye tests, consults and medical appointments with our optometrists; in a swift timely manner. On average, 24-32 patients for processing and testing, to then be allocated to 1 of 3 Optometrist clinics. As well as processing and filing of any relevant NHS/Government funded claims.
- Providing excellent support to patients in a one-on-one capacity with choosing and informing on products and services post appointment, as well as any unappointed walk in customers. Usually resulting in 15-30 personal full dispenses per shift.
- Striving to provide careful assistance to patients with ocular health concerns with 'Eye Health Concern' triaging. Applying my knowledge and skills to ensure patients receive all needed care for health concerns, whilst ensuring a swift, comfortable and stress free process for the patient.

#### **Bartender**

Heineken Franchise Pub - Stone December 2019 to March 2020

• Serving patrons various beverages and foods with pleasure and offering friendly polite conversation during appropriate periods.

- Maintaining a clean, organised bar and patron space in order for the establishment to be hygienic, welcoming and safe. Stocking and maintaining the fast moving stock from storerooms between duties.
- Setting up and maintaining the various pieces of bar equipment and ensuring swift reestablishment of supply when barrels run dry.

#### **Customer Assistant**

Wm Morrisons Supermarkets - Stone July 2015 to December 2019

- Carefully handling customer complaint and conflict issues on the complaints desk. Ensuring all product, service and cost issues raised by customers were resolved swiftly and with highest attainable customer satisfaction. Using interpersonal skills in order to deescalate any customer conflict that can arise during daily operations, striving to reverse any negative interaction in order for the customer to leave satisfied.
- Operating the store adjoined petrol fueling station, often in a lone capacity. Ensuring all through traffic of around 300-600 vehicles a shift was able to access our myriad services smoothly and swiftly, serving on foot customers. Facilitating the safe operation of the facility by ensuring all systems and machines are running safe and optimally, securing the premises as needed, and processing and securing large amounts of funds on a day to day basis.
- Happily and effectively offering assistance to customers and colleagues alike as I moved around my myriad daily roles.

#### **Customer Assistant**

Premier - Staffordshire November 2012 to July 2015

- Tending to customers in a friendly and personable manner, as the main clientele were local and regular. Exceeding efforts to maintain good relations with each one in order to maintain a happy and consistent customer base.
- Consistently maintain a clean, tidy and well stocked store. In order for our customers to have the ease of use of our facilities and keep a clean and professional visage.
- Ensuring stocked inventory, reordering as needed and securing of funds, and safely closing and securing the premises after daily operations.

### Education

#### **Level 2 in Business**

NCSC - Stafford June 2020 to December 2022

### **Level 2 in Electrical Engineering**

NCSC - Stafford September 2011 to February 2013

## **Level 2 in ICT and Business**

Stoke-on-Trent September 2010 to March 2011

# Skills

- Sales (2 years)
- Medical Scheduling (2 years)
- Computer skills (10+ years)
- Schedule Management (2 years)
- Microsoft Office (10+ years)
- Microsoft Excel (10+ years)
- Customer service (10+ years)
- Customer support (6 years)
- Conflict management (6 years)
- Optical experience (2 years)
- Communication skills (10+ years)